

Beata Greń-Onderko beongren@gmail.com (+44) 7448 245462 d.o.b.: 31st August 1963 Polish full driving license CRB on demand

Beata Greń-Onderko

Shop assistant

Career Profile I am outgoing and open-minded person. Specifically, I am open to the new challenges and always happy to start something new - moving to another country is quite an example. I am well organised and keen to details. I can work hard and as I live in the center of Ross-on-Wye - flexibility is also my virtue.

Key experience Now I am working full time in Euro Garages (Ross on Wye) . I started working there as a sales assitant at 17th May and my duties includes :

1. The till:

- selling petrol
- selling non-petrol items
- promotions
- coupons

2. The garage shop:

- stock the shelves
- keeping workspace clean and tidy
- cleaning the coffee machine

This is a very demanding job that requires <u>fast reaction</u>, the excellent <u>communications skills</u>, the ability to <u>concentrate on multiple things at one time</u> and to work under quite a pressure sometimes.

Work experience

17th May 2016 - ...

Sales assistant in Euro Garages (Ross-On-Wye) FULL TIME

8th May 2016 - ...

Cleaner (PART TIME) at Parkfields Country House. Duties: keeping all areas of Parkfields Country house clean and tidy, sorting laundry, dusting, polishing, sweeping.

September 2015-April 2016

Au pair for two children : girl 22 months, girl 4.5 years old in Ross-on-Wye, UK

October 1986-June 1987

Afternoon babysitting in family orphanage: girl(8 years old); boy (8 years old); girl aged 12 with schizophrenia;

1988-89

24h/7 babysitting of 9-month old baby girl;

July 1990-August 1991

Au pair in Ventabren, France; 2 children: boy aged 1,5 and boy aged 3 as well as taking care of the house (cleaning, cooking, laundry etc.)

Training and Courses

03rd October 1985 -19th May 1986

First aid course at Polish Red Cross at PRC Wrocław

August 1986

One month <u>language scholarship</u> founded by French Embassy at University of Grenoble, France

02nd March 2009-30th June 2009

Training in Social Integration Center (Centrum Integracji Społecznej) in Wrocław. Aim: schooling in licensing and running social cooperative (446 hours)

10th September 2009-19th December 2009

English language course at Pre-Intermediate level in Yellow Language Center Sp. z.o.o (64 hours)

January - August 2010

Participation in "Women professionally active- It's me" project concerning: 60h of <u>UE projects management</u> training, 8h of <u>labour legislation</u> training, 30h of <u>computer skills</u> training (MS Office), 8h of <u>labour market</u> training, 8h of <u>psychology</u> workshop, 8h <u>auto presentation</u> skills training, english language course finished with TOEIC exam

2009-2011

French language course at level B2/C1 in Alliance Français Language School in Wrocław (3 semesters)

October 2014-July 2015

English language course at A2 level (coursebook A2/B1) with final exam

Education

1982-1987

Studies at Faculty of National Economics at Oskar Lange's Academy of Economics (now University of Economics) in Wrocław

Skills and Interests

Languages

Interests

- \circ Natural medicine \circ Sports: fitness and \circ Films and festivals and herbalism skiing
- Gardening Classical music

References

References upon request.